Guide to the Biographical Information on Yale University Affiliated Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Biographical information on Yale University affiliated individuals
1858-2009
RU 237
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
35.75
(53 boxes)
The records consist of biographies, vitae, photographs and related materials documenting the careers of members of the Yale community.
Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-C (YRG 4-C), Records documenting public information functions of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of biographies, vitae, photographs and related materials documenting the careers of members of the Yale community.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College teachers; Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Universities and colleges -- Faculty; Photographs; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. Office of Public Affairs
- Faculty vitae, 1938-1985; Accession 1988-A-057 (Box 1–30)
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Faculty vitae, press releases and clippings, 1972-1988; Accession 1991-A-038
  - Acheson, David (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Norman I., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Richard D. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Robert, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ahlstrom, Sidney E. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alssen, Judith L. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Akpaide, Uko W. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albert, Daniel M. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alger, Jeffry R. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Altholz, Robert (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anderson, Robert G., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Andrews, Dwight D. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Angell, Katharine C. (Mrs. James Rowland Angell) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Appiah, Anthony (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Archibald, Elizabeth (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Archibald, J. David (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Armstrong, Robert, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arndla, Douglas M. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Arrom, Sylvia M. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arterton, Christopher (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ashburn, Frank (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bainton, Roland (Rev.) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Balay, Robert E. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Balmer, Jane E. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Baron, Larry (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Barron, Donald H. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bars, Itzhak (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bartholomew, Marshall (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Barzelay, Ross (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Baue, Arthur E., Dr. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bavier, Anne R. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bean, Susan S. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Beck, Fred J. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Beggs, John J. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Behr, Richard H. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Benston, Kimberly M. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Berger, Charles (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bernard, Jonathan W. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Berry, Joseph K. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Biersteker, Thomas S. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bigelow, John P. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bishop, Courtney, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bishop, Joseph, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Black, Barbara A. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Black, John b. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Blinder, David (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bowden, William b. (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Braceland, Francis, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Brady, Frank (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Breakefield, Xandra O. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Brown, Charles S. (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Brown, Stephen J. J. (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Burt, Ellen S. (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Caldwell, C. Denise (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Calhoun, Robert L. (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Cambell, Gretna (Box 1, Folder 55a)
  - Carr, Canon b. (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Carroll, Richard C. (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Caserio, Robert L. (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Cash, Robin (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Chan, Tony (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Charney, Ruth (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Charpentier, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Chaudry, Irshad H. (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Cherry, Edward E. (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Chiel, Arthur A. (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Chilton, Bruce D. (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Chrisman, Bruce L. (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Cizewski, Jolie A. (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Clark, John D. (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Clark, Terri P. (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Clouet, Herbert A. (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Cole, Edward C. (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Contreras, Robert J. (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Cooper, Russell W. (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Corey, David P. (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Cornell, Robert W. (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Cornog, John, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Couch, A. Edward (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Cover, Robert M. (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Cox, Martha G. (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Crafton, Donald (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Crosby, Faye (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Crosby, Sumner McK. (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Cunningham, Peter, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Currie, Steven R. (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Curtin, Phyllis (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Darnell, Regna (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Daver, Edward A. (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Davie, James S. (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Davis, Kenneth P. (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Davis-Friedmann, Deborah (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Dayan, Joan (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - DeJean, Joan E. (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Delap, Robert J. (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Dellore, Mairead H. (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - DeLuca, Donald R. (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Dembo, Ron S. (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Demetz, Hana (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Dihoff, Ivan R. (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Dobie, Albert R. (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Donabedian, Richard (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Donovan, Constance (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Dow, Gregory (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Dubin, Lois C. (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Dunlop, Margaret (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Dwyer, John M. (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Dye, Victor C. (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Earley, Michael (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Eaton, Jonathan (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Eckstein, Zvi (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Edelstein, Teri (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Egan, Margarita (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Egan, Patrick O. (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Engley, Donald b. (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Ernest, Michael J. (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Evans, Theodore, Dr. (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Ewing, Lucia P. (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Fairbanks, Charles, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Fellner, William J. (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Ferguson, Margaret (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Ferlo, Roger A. (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Filer, John H. (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Fischer, John M. (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Fishkin, James Steven (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Fishkin, Shelley M.f. (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Fishlow, Albert (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Fitzpatrick, Eugene (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Flom, Leonard (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Flye, Wayne (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Foltz, Anne-Marie (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Franklin, Vincent P. (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Fries, Marilyn Sibley (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Gabriel, Ralph (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Gariepy, Thomas P. (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Garratt, George A. (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Gates, Henry L., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Gaudon, Jean A. M. (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Geha, Alexander S., Dr. (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Gershon, Richard K. (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Gersick, Connie (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Getman, Julius G. (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Gibble, Kenneth (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Gilmore, Grant (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Gleason, Joan Marie (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Goff, Genevieve (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Goldenberg, Ira S. (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Gonzalez, Shirley (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Goodman, Lawrence G. (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Greenberg, Irwin M. (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Greengard, Paul (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Gregory, Jack (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Greig, Ann Elizabeth (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Griffiths, John (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Gross, Jan Tomasz (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Guerlac, Suzanne (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Hackman, J. Richard (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Haight, Gordon S. (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Halperin, Daniel (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Halsey, Ralph W., III (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Hamabata, Matthews M. (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Hammond, David A. (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Handel, Steven (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Hanna, Archibald, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Hardy, James, Dr. (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Harrell, Martha (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Harris, Benedict, Dr. (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Harrison, John A. (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Harrison, Richard (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Harvard, b. Marvin (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Harvey, Mary (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Harwood, William (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Hays, Richard b. (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Hazle, Nancy (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Headington, Charles E. (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Hedlund, Nancy L. (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Heller, Joan (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Hendel, Charles W. (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Henson, David b. (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Herek, Gregory M. (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Herken, Gregg (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Herman, John C. (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Herold, Wolf-Dietrich (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Hinger, Fred D. (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Hirshfield, Jay L. (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Hiscock, Ira V. (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Hodson, Cecil J., Dr. (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Hoffman, Edward C. (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Hogan, C. Beecher (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Holcombe, Marya W. (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Holgate, James (Gib) (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Holme, Thomas T. (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Holzer, Charles, III (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Houghton, Walter Edwards (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Hughes, Edward J. (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Hughes, Roger L. (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Hummel, David M. (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Ingholt, Harald (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Jackson, Timothy P. (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Jaeger, Robert A. (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Jameson, Frederic R. (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - Jenson, Mogens R. (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Johnson, Barbara E. (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Johnson, Bonny L. (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - Johnson, Tony (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - Johnston, David C. (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - Jones, Stephen b. (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - Kahler, Miles (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - Kanter, Rosabeth Moss (Box 2, Folder 208-209)
  - Kao, Karl S. Y. (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Kaplan, Amy (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - Kauffmann, Stanley (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - Keitel, Elizabeth (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - Kelsey, Jennifer L. (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Keyes, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - Kiang, Lindsey C. Y. (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - Kibbey, Ann M. (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - Kimberly, John R. (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - Kirkpatrick, Ralph (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - Kirschner, Shirley M. (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - Kittel, Bonnie P. (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - Klatskin, Gerald (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - Knollmueller, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - Knowlton, Nancy (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - Koch, Peter M. (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - Konopacki, Steven A. (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - Korner, Ann M. (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - Kramer, Patricia (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - Kranakis, Eda (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - Krieger, Karenf. (Box 2, Folder 230)
  - Krishnan, Mahadevan (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Kueffner, William (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - Kugel, James (Box 2, Folder 233)
  - Kurtz, Martha (Box 2, Folder 234)
  - Labaree, Leonard (Box 2, Folder 235)
  - Lachmann, Renate (Box 2, Folder 236)
  - Lambert, James W. (Box 2, Folder 237)
  - Lambert, Paul (Box 2, Folder 238)
  - Landmesser, Lynn (Box 2, Folder 239)
  - Large, David Clay (Box 2, Folder 240)
  - Lehnert, Wendy G. (Box 2, Folder 241)
  - Leitch, Thomas M. (Box 2, Folder 242)
  - Lerner, Marguerite L. (Box 2, Folder 243)
  - Lewin, David b. (Box 2, Folder 244)
  - Lewis, Helen Block (Box 2, Folder 245)
  - Lifton, Robert J. (Box 2, Folder 246)
  - Lindenmuth, Woodrow (Box 2, Folder 247)
  - Lipsky, Seymour (Box 2, Folder 248)
  - Lipson, Kyoko K. (Box 2, Folder 249)
  - Livesky, Robert S. (Box 2, Folder 250)
  - Lopez, Robert S. (Box 2, Folder 251)
  - Lifton, Robert J. (Box 2, Folder 252)
  - Lovett, Sidney J. (The Reverend) (Box 2, Folder 253)
  - Lardy, Nicholas R. (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Lull, David J. (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Lustig, Irma S. (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Lydon, Roy T. (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Lyons, William (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - MacAvoy, Paul W. (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - MacClintock, Copeland (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - MacIntyre, Angus J. (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - MacKenzie, Ken (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - McCrillis, John (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - McDonough, Paul A. (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - McGerr, Michael E. (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - McGuire, Edward (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - McKay, David b. (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - McMullan, Sandra H. (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Maewal, Akhilesh (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Malamat, Abraham (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Malkiel, Burton G. (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Mandel, Henry R. (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Markert, Clement (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Marston, Thomas E. (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Martens, Lorna (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Matter, Herbert (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - Mauceri, Johnf. (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - May, Carl J. (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - Mejia, Berta A. (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - Messer, Ellen (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Meurman, Arne (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - Meyer, Jerrilyn H. (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Meyer, Walter H. (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - Migiel, Marilyn (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - Milgrom, Paul R. (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - Miller, Martha (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - Milofsky, Carl (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - Minrath, Marilyn (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - Moehlman, Patricia D. (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Mohr, Peter J. (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Moore, Charles W. (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - Morf, Martin (Box 3, Folder 292)
  - Morgus, Wallace (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Morris, Christopher (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Moskaluk, Walter P. (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Mudgett, Kathryn E. (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - Muldoon, Maggie (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Munro, Barbara H. (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Murnane, Richard J. (Box 3, Folder 299)
  - Mylon, Ermst (Box 3, Folder 300)
  - Nauseef, William M. (Box 3, Folder 301)
  - Naydan, Michael M. (Box 3, Folder 302)
  - Neale, William H., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 303)
  - Nelson, Richard R. (Box 3, Folder 304)
  - Nemoy, Leon (Box 3, Folder 305)
  - Nichols, Carol W. (Box 3, Folder 306)
  - Nishimura, Yukiko K. (Box 3, Folder 307)
  - Nolan, William J. (Box 3, Folder 308)
  - Nordlund, James J. (Box 3, Folder 309)
  - Norton, Linda J. C. (Box 3, Folder 310)
  - Norton, Nea M. (Box 3, Folder 311)
  - Noyes, Edward M. (Box 3, Folder 312)
  - O"Brien, Patricia (Box 3, Folder 313)
  - Odendahl, Teresa J. (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - O"Donnell, Edward (Box 3, Folder 315)
  - Ogden, John A. (Box 3, Folder 316)
  - Okal, Emil A. (Box 3, Folder 317)
  - Olsen, Randall J. (Box 3, Folder 318)
  - Olzak, Susan (Box 3, Folder 319)
  - Onat, Etta (Box 3, Folder 320)
  - Oulianoff, Nicolas (Box 3, Folder 321)
  - Owen, Stephen (Box 3, Folder 322)
  - Papaefstratiou, Louka T. Katseli (Box 3, Folder 323)
  - Parker, Patricia A. (Box 3, Folder 324)
  - Parker, Yvonne (Box 3, Folder 325)
  - Patrick, Hugh Talbot (Box 3, Folder 326)
  - Paulson, Ronald (Box 3, Folder 327)
  - Pearson, Geraldine (Box 3, Folder 328)
  - Petryn, Andrewf. (Box 3, Folder 329)
  - Philippi, Dale (Box 3, Folder 330)
  - Phillips, Aris (Box 3, Folder 331)
  - Pincus, Cynthia S. (Box 3, Folder 332)
  - Pincus, Jonathan (Box 3, Folder 333)
  - Piotrkowski, Chaya (Box 3, Folder 334)
  - Pippin, Paul W. T. (Box 3, Folder 335)
  - Platt Terry (Box 3, Folder 336)
  - Poling, Wesley H. (Box 3, Folder 337)
  - Pottle, Frederick A. (Box 3, Folder 338)
  - Potts, Richards (Box 3, Folder 339)
  - Price, Derek deSolla (Box 3, Folder 340)
  - Prosnitz, Leonard (Box 3, Folder 341)
  - Provasoli, Luigi (Box 3, Folder 342)
  - Puklin, James E. (Box 3, Folder 343)
  - Putt, Frederick A. (Box 3, Folder 344)
  - Quilligan, Maureen (Box 3, Folder 345)
  - Rabinovitch, Judith N. (Box 3, Folder 346)
  - Ramsbottom, Mary M. (Box 3, Folder 347)
  - Ramsey, Gordon C. (Box 3, Folder 348)
  - Rassner, Ronald M. (Box 3, Folder 349)
  - Reid, Ted W. (Box 3, Folder 350)
  - Rethis, Michael (Box 3, Folder 351)
  - Rhoads, Donald C. (Box 3, Folder 352)
  - Rhoads, John G. (Box 3, Folder 353)
  - Righter, James V. (Box 3, Folder 354)
  - Riley, Helene (Box 3, Folder 355)
  - Rivers, Elias L. (Box 3, Folder 356)
  - Robertson, Leon (Box 3, Folder 357)
  - Robinson, Rachel (Box 3, Folder 358)
  - Rodgers, Beckett M. (Box 3, Folder 359)
  - Rodman, James E. (Box 3, Folder 360)
  - Rodriguez-Monegal, Emir (Box 3, Folder 361)
  - Rogovin, Roberta (Box 3, Folder 362)
  - Rose, Gilbert (Box 3, Folder 363)
  - Rosenstone, Steven (Box 3, Folder 364)
  - Rothblum, Uriel G. (Box 3, Folder 365)
  - Rothenberg, Albert (Box 3, Folder 366)
  - Rotkovitch, Rachel (Box 3, Folder 367)
  - Rowe, David N. (Box 3, Folder 368)
  - Rowthorn, Jeffrey (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - Rush, James R. (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Russell, Conrad S. R. (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Rutenberg, Lauri (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - Ryerson, Ellen G. (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - Saad, Youcef (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Sachs, Jeffrey D. (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Sadler, Lois (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Safa-Isfehani, Nezhat (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Sarkonak, Ralph (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Savo, Cynthia (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Scammell, Harry D. (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - Scarr, Sandra (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - Schaus, N. A. (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Schilder, Donald P. (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Schmid, Rudolph (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - Schneer, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - Schultz, James A. (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - Schulz, Rose A. (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Seeley, Thomas D. (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - Serene, Joseph W. (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Shamansky, Sherry L. (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Sheldon, Wilmon H. (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Shemitz, Sylvan R. (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Shestack, Alan (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Shimada, Nadinef. (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - Shoaf, Richard H. (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Silverman, Jason H. (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Smith, David C. (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - Snavely, Deanne L. (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Snead, James A. (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - Snyder, Joseph C. (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - Solitaire, Gilbert b., Dr. (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - Spackman, Barbara (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - Steere, Allen C. (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - Steigman, Maury (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - Stepan, Alfred C. (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - Stern, Robert A. M. (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - Stern, Stanley (Box 4, Folder 407)
  - Stevens, Barbara (Box 4, Folder 408)
  - Stirling, Jamesf. (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - Stokes, Rev. Alison (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - Storrs, David (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - Storer, Edward H., Dr. (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - Story, Larry (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Straker, Ian b. (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - Strasberger, Dr. Victor (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - Swift, William E. (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - Taft, Horace D. (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Taube, Steven, Dr. (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Tennant, Mary E. (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Tepperman, Lorne J. (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Thalmann, William G. (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - Thier, Samuel D., Dr. (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - Thompson, Bradbury (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - Thompson, Hughes (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - Tiffney, Bruce H. (Box 4, Folder 425)
  - Tifft, Stephen (Box 4, Folder 426)
  - Tilson, Catherine S. (Mrs. John Q., Jr.) (Box 4, Folder 427)
  - Tippo, Denis R. (Box 4, Folder 428)
  - Tirella, Fred Francis (Box 4, Folder 429)
  - Tower, Roni Beth (Box 4, Folder 430)
  - Tracey, Robert (Box 4, Folder 431)
  - Turk, Dennis (Box 4, Folder 432)
  - Turner, Hazel M. (Crawford) (Box 4, Folder 433)
  - Tze, Hsiung Chia (Box 4, Folder 434)
  - Underwood, Arthur H. (The Reverend) (Box 4, Folder 435)
  - Urbin, Mary Ann (Box 4, Folder 436)
  - Vaill, George D. (Box 4, Folder 437)
  - Vannorsdall, John W. (The Reverend) (Box 4, Folder 438)
  - Vietzke, Wesley M., Dr. (Box 4, Folder 439)
  - Von Eckhardt, Barbara (Box 4, Folder 440)
  - Vonkoss, Heidi M. (Box 4, Folder 441)
  - Wahba, Grace (Box 4, Folder 442)
  - Wahlquist, Irene (Box 4, Folder 443)
  - Wang, Deane (Box 4, Folder 444)
  - Ward, Deborah H. (Box 4, Folder 445)
  - Weeks, Kathleen Mary (Box 4, Folder 446)
  - Weinberger, Naomi Joy (Box 4, Folder 447)
  - Weinstein, Jerome L. (Box 4, Folder 448)
  - Weiskel, Timothy C. (Box 4, Folder 449)
  - Weiss, Janet (Box 4, Folder 450)
  - Weller, Martha R. (Box 4, Folder 451)
  - Weller, Robert A. (Box 4, Folder 452)
  - Welliver, Neil (Box 4, Folder 453)
  - Wenzel, Helene V. (Box 4, Folder 454)
  - Wertheimer, David M. (Box 4, Folder 454A)
  - Westbrook, Robert (Box 4, Folder 455)
  - Wheaton, R. Blair (Box 4, Folder 456)
  - Weinert, T. A. (Box 4, Folder 457)
  - Wiesel, Elie (Box 4, Folder 458)
  - Williams, Colin W. (The Reverend) (Box 4, Folder 459)
  - Williams, Georgef. (Box 4, Folder 460)
  - Williams, Naomi Joy (Box 4, Folder 461)
  - Williamson, Kerry A. (Box 4, Folder 462)
  - Willinger, Steve (Box 4, Folder 463)
  - Winn, James A. (Box 4, Folder 464)
  - Wippern, Ronaldf. (Box 4, Folder 465)
  - Wolfgang, Richard L. (Box 4, Folder 466)
  - Wolpin, Kenneth I. (Box 4, Folder 467)
  - Woodford, Patricia T. (Box 4, Folder 468)
  - Wright, Brian O. (Box 4, Folder 469)
  - Yates, Douglas T., Jr. (Box 4, Folder 470)
  - Yeager, Peter C. (Box 4, Folder 471)
  - Yu, Kai Fun (Box 4, Folder 472)
  - Yu, Ying-Shih (Box 4, Folder 473)
  - Zornig, John Grant (Box 4, Folder 474)
  - Abzug, Bella, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 475)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 476)
  - Anfinsen, Christian, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 477)
  - Armstrong, J. Neil, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 478)
  - Ashe, Arthur, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 479)
  - Ashbery, John, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 480)
  - Askew, Reubin, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 481)
  - Bam, Brigalla, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 482)
  - Barak, Aharon, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 483)
  - Barrow, Errol, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 484)
  - Belgium, King and Queen of, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 485)
  - Bell, Griffin, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 486)
  - Bellamy, Carol (Box 5, Folder 487)
  - Berlin, Sir Isaiah, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 488)
  - Bernstein, Carl, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - Berrigan, Father Daniel, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 490)
  - Black, Shirley Temple, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 491)
  - Blair, James, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - Blair, S. Robert, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  - Borman, Frank, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 494)
  - Bowater, Lord and Lady, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 495)
  - Boyer, Ernest L., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 496)
  - Bradlee, Benjamin, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 497)
  - Brock, Bill, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 498)
  - Broder, David, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 499)
  - Brodsky, Joseph, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 500)
  - Brown, Esther, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  - Brown, Edmund G. ("Jerry"), 1976 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  - Bush, George, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - (missed number) (Box 5, Folder 504)
  - Cage, John, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 505)
  - Canadian Ambassador, Jack H. Warren, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 506)
  - Carillo, Santiago, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 507)
  - Carstens, Karl, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 508)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 509)
  - Castillo, Leonel, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 510)
  - Cheever, John, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 511)
  - China, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 512)
  - China: PRC Ministry of Education, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 513)
  - Church, Frank, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 514)
  - Cleary, Catherine, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 515)
  - Coffin, William S., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 516)
  - Commoner, Barry, undated (Box 5, Folder 517)
  - Cooke, Alistair, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 518)
  - Cooper, Richard (Box 5, Folder 519)
  - Copland, Aaron, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 520)
  - Cosell, Howard, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 521)
  - Cotton,f. Albert, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 522)
  - Cox, Archibald, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 523)
  - Darity, William, Dr., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 524)
  - Dayan, Moshe, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 525)
  - Dean, John, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 526)
  - De Bakey, Michael, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 527)
  - De Carolis, Massimo, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 528)
  - Dilieto, Police Chief, undated (Box 5, Folder 529)
  - Didion, Joan, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 530)
  - Dinitz, Simcha, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 531)
  - Doctorow, E. L., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 532)
  - Drinan, Robert, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 533)